# Matthew Wall

in matthewtwall | waltersavenger.github.io | matthewtwall@outlook.com | +513-254-2700

# Summary

Earned a degree in Mathematics and Audio Engineering Technology with over 5 years experience as a software developer. Strong innovative mindset to contribute to a companies' product. Dedicated to the opportunities presented. Proficiency with managing projects and clients independently. Seeking an opportunity to work in an environment that challenges skill set.

# Work Experience

#### TrackAbout, Software Engineer

Jun 2021 - present

- Develop and implement new features including a new standalone application for internal tooling. This process includes requirement gathering, designing, developing, PM approval, QA, client-testing, and post deployment processing.
- Be the main point of contact for our support team to analyze issues that arise and determine both short- and long-term solutions for over 300 clients for Android, IOS, and Web .Net Applications.
- Development process includes unit test writing, integration test writing, database procedure writing, database performance tuning, deployment scripting, and documentation.

#### North American Stainless, Software Engineer

Jul 2020 - Jun 2021

- Maintain and improve AngularJS intranet reporting application, SQL databases, backend math models, Window's Services, and WPF MVC applications according to requests or issues.
- Develop, test, and implement WPF MVC apps, Windows Services, and legacy software to control rolling mills, report data sets, and communicate with other software systems within the plant.

#### FAST Enterprises, Implementation Consultant

Aug 2018 - May 2020

- Thoroughly tested and documented development changes from client regs through testing environments with proper communication, regression testing, and change specific test scenarios.
- Collected client requirements, developed new software for government agency ensuring it would fit legacy data, and created SQL queries to determine data needs and for reporting purposes.
- Development tasks included building webservices, querying and manipulating the database, creating GUI populating code (as well as new GUIs), creating automation processes and other back end and front-end development tasks.

### EDUCATION

2014 - 2018 Bachelor of Science, Mathematics and Audio Engineering Technology

Undergraduate Research Fellowships in the Sciences 2017

Belmont University (GPA: 3.42)

# SKILLS

CSS, C#, C++, HTML, Java, Javascript, Python, SQL, TypeScript, VB.net, XML Languages

Azure, AWS, Git, NUnit, Redis, Resharper, SSRS, Visual Studio, Xamarin Technologies

Other Arduino, database design, home automation, network design, requirement gathering